<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<doc><id>48</id><url>http://yjs.njupt.edu.cn/epstar/web/outer/dsfc_ny_.jsp?dsgh=20070176</url><title>李云</title><datetime>2018-09-12</datetime><body>
									（1）机器学习和数据挖掘的理论、算法及应用，特别关注高维复杂数据的维数约简、大规模数据的学习、安全机器学习和未标记数据的利用问题。并将研究成果应用到信息安全、信号处理和认知无线电等；（2）利用高性能计算或分布式计算解决大规模机器学习问题；（3）机器学习和生物信息学的交叉研究；（4）模式识别，主要研究基于生物特征的医疗健康监测技术。代表性论文：[1] Yun Li, Jennie Si, Guojing Zhou, Shasha Huang and Songcan Chen. “FREL:A stable feature selection algorithm”. IEEE Trans. Neural Networks and Learning Systems, vol.26, pp.1388-1402, 2015. [2] Yun Li, Suyan Gao and Songcan Chen. “Ensemble feature weighting based on local learning and diversity”. Twenty-Sixth Conf. Artificial Intelligence (AAAI), vol.2, pp.1019-1025, Toronto, Canada, 2012.[3] Yun Li and Bao-Liang Lu. “Feature selection based on loss-margin of nearest neighbor classification”. Pattern Recognition, vol.42, pp.1914-1921, 2009. [4] Yun Li and Zhong-Fu Wu. “Fuzzy feature selection based on min-max learning rule and extension matrix”. Pattern Recognition, vol.41, pp. 217-226, 2008. [5] Yun Li, Jun Yang, Wei Ji. Local learning-based feature weighting with privacy preservation. Neurocomputing, vol. 174, pp. 1107-1115, 2016.[6] Wei Ji and Yun Li. “Stable dysphonia measures selection for Parkinson speech rehabilitation via diversity regularized ensemble”. Proc. 41st IEEE Int’l Conf. on Acoustics, Speech and Signal Processing( ICASSP), Shanghai, P. R. China, 2016.[7] Peng Yan and Yun Li. “Graph-Margin Based Multi-Label Feature Selection”. European Conference on Machine Learning, ECML, Riva del Garda, Italy, 2016.[8] Yingxiang Huang, Yun Li and Baohua Qiang. “Internet traffic classification based on min-max ensemble feature selection”. Proc. Int’l Joint Conf. on Neural Networks (IJCNN), pp. 3485-3492, Vancouver, Canada, 2016.[9] Wei Ji, Yun Li and Kejia Chen. “Local energy-based framework for feature ranking”. Journal of Intelligent &amp; Fuzzy Systems, vol. 28, pp. 1565-1575, 2015. [10] Yanping Wu and Yun Li. “Semi-supervised Min-Max Modular SVM”. Int’l Joint Conf. Neural Networks (IJCNN), Killarney, Ireland, 2015.[11] Jun Yang and Yun Li, “Differentially private feature selection”, Proc. Int’l Joint Conf. on Neural Networks (IJCNN), pp.4182-4189, 2014.[12 Kai Chen, Wenqiang Wan and Yun Li. “Differentially private feature selection under MapReduce framework”, The Journal of China Universities of Posts and Telecommunications, vol. 20(5), pp.85-90, 2013.[13] Yun Li, Shasha Huang, Songcan Chen and Jennie Si. “Stable L2-regularized ensemble feature weighting”, Int’l Workshop on Multiple Classifier Systems (MCS), Lecture Notes in Computer Sciences (LNCS), vol.7872, pp.167-178, 2013.[14] Wei Ji and Yun Li. “Energy-based feature ranking for assessing the dysphonia measurements in parkinson detection”, IET Signal Processing, vol.6(4), pp. 300-305, 2012.[15] Yun Li and Li-Li Feng. “Integrating feature selection and min-max modular SVM for powerful ensemble”. Int’l Joint Conf. Neural Networks (IJCNN), vol.1, pp.1-8, Brisbane, Australia, 2012. [16] Yun Li and Su-Yan Gao. “Energy-based feature selection and its ensemble version”, Int’l Conf. Neural Information Processing (ICONIP), Lecture Notes in Computer Science (LNCS), vol.7063, pp.53-62, 2011. [17] Xiao-Min Xie and Yun Li. “Bisecting data partitioning methods for min-max modular support vector machine”, IEEE Int’l Conf. Fuzzy System and Knowledge Discovery (FSKD), pp.992-996, 2011. [18] Yun Li, Bao-Liang Lu and Teng-Fei Zhang. “Combining feature selection with extraction: unsupervised feature selection based on principal component analysis”. International Journal on Artificial Intelligence Tools, vol.18, pp.883-904, 2009. [19] Yun Li, Su-Jun Hu, Wen-Jie Yang, Guo-Zi Sun, Fang-Wu Yao and Geng Yang. “Similarity-based feature selection for learning from examples with continuous values”. Pacific-Asia Conf. on Knowledge Discovery and Data Mining (PAKDD), Lecture Notes in Artificial Intelligence (LNAI), vol.5476, pp.957-964, Bangkok, Thailand, 2009. [20] Yun Li, Bao-Liang Lu and Zhong-Fu Wu, “Hierarchical fuzzy filter method for unsupervised feature selection”. Journal of Intelligent &amp; Fuzzy Systems, vol.18, pp.157-169, 2007. [21] Yun Li, Bao-Liang Lu and Zhong-Fu Wu. “A hybrid method of unsupervised feature selection based on ranking”. Proc. of Int’l Conf. on Pattern Recognition (ICPR), pp.687-690, Hong Kong, P. R. China, 2006.
</body></doc>