<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<doc><id>57</id><url>http://yjs.njupt.edu.cn/epstar/web/outer/dsfc_ny_.jsp?dsgh=20090021</url><title>陈可佳</title><datetime>2018-09-12</datetime><body>
									目前本人主要研究方向为机器学习、数据挖掘、复杂网络分析等。部分成果如下：K.-J. Chen, K. Zhang, X.-L. Jiang. Transfer learning with active queries for relational data modeling across multiple information networks. In: Proceedings of the 25th International Conference on Neural Information Processing (ICONIP), 2018.Y. Wang, J. Zhai, Y. Li, K.-J. Chen, H. Xue. Transfer learning with partial related "instance-feature" knowledge. Neurocomputing, 2018, 310: 115-124.K.-J. Chen, S. Xue, Y. Li, B. Liu. On link formation in heterogeneous information networks: a view based on multi-label learning. In: Proceedings of the IEEE/ACM International Conference on Advances in Social Networks Analysis and Mining (ASONAM), 2017, 50-53.G.-J. Peng, K.-J. Chen, S. Xue, B. Liu. A relation prediction method based on PU learning. In: Proceedings of the 12th International Conference on Intelligent Systems and Knowledge Engineering, 2017.Y. Wang, J. Zhou, K.-J. Chen, Y. Wang, L. Liu. Water quality prediction method based on LSTM neural network. In: Proceedings of the 12th International Conference on Intelligent Systems and Knowledge Engineering, 2017.B. Liu, K.-J. Chen. Maximum likelihood estimation based on random subspace EDA: application to extrasolar planet detection. In: Proceedings of the 11th International Conference on Simulated Evolution and Learning, 2017, 3-14.H. Xu, B. Liu, K.-J. Chen. iTrace: an implicit trust inference method for trust-aware collaborative filtering. CoRR abs/1708.03658, 2017: 040102.K.-J. Chen, Y. Chen, Y. Li, J. Han. A supervised link prediction method for dynamic networks. Journal of Intelligent and Fuzzy Systems, 2016, 31(1): 291-299.J. Han, K.-J. Chen, J. Wang. Web article quality ranking based on web community knowledge. Computing, 2015, 97(5): 509-537.W. Ji, Y. Li, K.-J. Chen, G. Zhou. Local energy-based framework for feature ranking. Journal of Intelligent and Fuzzy Systems, 2015, 28(4): 1565-1575.Y. Chen, K.-J. Chen, Y. Li. A link prediction method that can learn from network dynamics. In: Proceedings of the 4th IEEE ICDM Workshop on Data Mining in Networks (ICDMW), 2014, 549-553.K.-J. Chen, Q. Zhu, J. Han, Z. Zheng. A time-aware link prediction approach based on semi-supervised learning. Journal of Information and Computational Science, 2014，6(2): 4593-4600.J. Han, K.-J. Chen, Z. Ding, H. Cao. An efficient location reporting and indexing framework for urban road moving objects. Distributed and Parallel Databases, 2014, 32(2): 271-311.J. Han, K.-J. Chen. Ranking Wikipedia article's data quality by learning dimension distributions. International Journal of Information Quality, 2014, 3(3): 207-227.J. Han, K.-J. Chen, Z. Zheng, Y. Yang. Assessment of web article's completeness by capturing discussed topics. International Journal of Web Engineering and Technology, 2014, 9(3): 247-276.Z. Zheng, K.-J. Chen, S. Zhang, H. Zhang. A link prediction approach using semi-supervised learning in dynamic networks. In: Proceedings the 6th International Conference on Advanced Computational Intelligence, 2013, 276-280.J. Han, K.-J. Chen, D. Jiang. Probabilistically ranking web article quality based on evolution patterns. Transactions on Large-Scale Data- and Knowledge-Centered Systems, 2012, 6: 229-258.J. Han, X. Chen, K.-J. Chen, D. Jiang. Assessing web article quality by harnessing collective intelligence. In: Proceedings of the 17th International Conference of Database Systems for Advanced Applications (DASFAA), 2012, 1: 428-439.J. Han, X. Fu, K.-J. Chen, C. Wang. Web article quality assessment in multi-dimensional space. In: Proceedings of the 12th Web-Age Information Management, 2011: 214-225.K.-J. Chen, J.-P. Barthès. A case-based memory mechanism for personal assistant agents. International Journal of Software Science and Computational Intelligence, 2010, 4(1): 45-64.K.-J. Chen, J.-P. Barthès. Giving an office assistant agent a memory mechanism. In: Proceedings of the 7th IEEE International Conference on Cognitive Informatics, 2008, 402-410. K.-J. Chen, J.-P. Barthès. MemoPA: intelligent personal assistant agents with a case memory mechanism. In: Proceedings of the 3th International Conference on Intelligent Computing, 2007, 1357-1367.K.-J. Chen, J.-P. Barthès. Enhancing intelligence of personal assistant agent using memory mechanism. In: Proceedings of the 11th International Conference on CSCW in Design, 2007, 361-365.Z.-H. Zhou, K.-J. Chen, H.-B. Dai. Enhancing relevance feedback in image retrieval using unlabeled data. ACM Transactions on Information Systems, 2006, 24(2): 219-244.Z.-H. Zhou, K.-J. Chen, Y. Jiang. Exploiting unlabeled data in content-based image retrieval. In: Proceedings of the 15th European Conference on Machine Learning (ECML), 2004, 525-536.Z.-H. Zhou, M.-L. Zhang, K.-J. Chen. A novel bag generator for image database retrieval with multi-instance learning techniques. In: Proceedings of the 15th IEEE International Conference on Tools with Artificial Intelligence (ICTAI), 2003, 565-569.Y. Jiang, K.-J. Chen, Z.-H. Zhou. SOM-based image segmentation. In: Proceedings of the 9th International Conference on Rough Sets, Fuzzy Sets, Data Mining and Granular Computing, 2003, 640-643.
</body></doc>