<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<doc><id>66</id><url>http://yjs.njupt.edu.cn/epstar/web/outer/dsfc_ny_.jsp?dsgh=20120124</url><title>刘斌</title><datetime>2018-09-12</datetime><body>
									研究方向：1. 算法研究：包括贝叶斯推理、机器学习、不确定性建模、统计计算等；2. 应用研究：主要面向网络及大数据等相关领域；论文代表作：1. Liu, B., Posterior Exploration based Sequential Monte Carlo for Global Optimization, Journal of Global Optimization, vol.69, no.4, pp.847-868, 2017. (SCI检索, 中国计算机学会推荐的、计算机科学理论方面的B类期刊)2. Dai, Y., Liu, B., Robust video object tracking via Bayesian model averaging based feature fusion, Optical Engineering, vol.55, no.8, pp.083102(1)-083102(11), 2016. (SCI检索，第一作者为所指导的研究生)3. Liu, B., Adaptive Annealed Importance Sampling for Multimodal Posterior Exploration and Model Selection with Application to Extrasolar Planet Detection, The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, vol. 213, no.14, pp.1-16, 2014. (SCI top期刊, 近三年平均影响因子&gt;10).4. Liu, B. and Ji, C., Bayesian Nonparametric Modeling for Rapid Design of Metamaterial Microstructures, International Journal of Antennas and Propagation, vol. 2014, pp.1-9, 2014. (SCI检索，主要内容涉及贝叶斯建模学习方法和优化设计)5. Liu, B., Instantaneous Frequency Tracking under Model Uncertainty via Dynamic Model Averaging and Particle Filtering, IEEE Trans. on Wireless Communications, vol.10, no.6, pp.1810-1819,2011. (SCI检索，主要内容涉及贝叶斯动态推理算法)6. Liu, B., Ji, C. and Zhang, Y., Hao, C. and Wong, K.K., Multi-target Tracking in Clutter with Sequential Monte Carlo Methods, IET Radar,Sonar,Navigation, vol.4, no.5, pp.662-672, 2010. (SCI检索)7. Liu, B., ILAPF: Incremental Learning Assisted Particle Filtering, Proc. of the 43rd IEEE International Conference on Acoustics, Speech and Signal Processing (ICASSP 2018), in press, Calgary, Alberta, Canada, 2018. (该会议为声学、语音和信号处理领域国际顶级会议)8. Liu, B., Robust Particle Filter by Dynamic Averaging of Multiple Noise Models, Proc. of the 42nd IEEE International Conference on Acoustics, Speech and Signal Processing (ICASSP 2017), pp.4034-4038, New Orleans, U.S., 2017. (该会议为声学、语音和信号处理领域国际顶级会议)9. Liu, B., Cheng, S. and Shi, Y., Improving Estimation of Distribution Algorithms with Heavy-Tailed Student's t Distributions, Proc. of 2018 10th International Conf. on Advanced Computational Intelligence (ICACI 2018),pp.6-11, Xiamen, China, 2018. (获最佳论文奖)10. Wang, J. and Liu, B., Online Fault-Tolerant Dynamic Event Region Detection in Sensor Networks via Trust Model, Proc. of IEEE Wireless Communications and Networking Conference (WCNC 2017), pp.1-6, San Francisco, CA, U.S., 2017. (第一作者为所指导的研究生，中国计算机学会推荐会议)更多论文信息见：https://www.researchgate.net/profile/Bin_Liu49 （可全文下载）
</body></doc>