<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<doc><id>78</id><url>http://yjs.njupt.edu.cn/epstar/web/outer/dsfc_ny_.jsp?dsgh=20140013</url><title>朱洁</title><datetime>2018-09-12</datetime><body>
									1. 研究方向[1]云计算相关开源项目研究： MapReduce/Hadoop、Dremel、Zookeeper、HDFS/Ceph、CloudFoundry、memcached[2]资源分配与调度算法研究2. 论文发表情况[1]Zhu J, Li X. Elastic and flexible multi-stage task scheduling with deadline-constraint in clouds.  The 20th IEEE International Conference on Computer Supported Cooperative Work in Design. 2016:286-291 （EI）[2]Zhu J, Li X, Ruiz R, et al. Scheduling Stochastic Multi-stage Jobs on Elastic Computing Services in Hybrid Clouds. IEEE International Conference on Web Services. IEEE Computer Society, 2016:678-681.[3]Zhu J, Li X. Scheduling for multi-stage applications with scalable virtual resources in cloud computing. International Journal of Machine Learning &amp; Cybernetics, 2016:1-9 (SCI)[4]Jie Zhu, Chao Sha. Multi-stage Scheduling with Scalable Resources for Automated Deployment in Platform as a Service Cloud. 2015 Seventh International Symposium on Parallel Architectures, Algorithms and Programming. 2015: 204-209. (EI)[5]Jie Zhu, Xiaoping Li. An effective meta-heuristic for no-wait job shops to minimize makespan. IEEE Transactions on Automation Science and Engineering. 2012, 9(1): 189-198 （SCI源，计算机学会推荐B类国际期刊）[6]Jie Zhu, Xiaoping Li, Qian Wang. Complete Local Search with Limited Memory Algorithm for No-Wait Job Shops to Minimize Makespan. European Journal of Operational Research. 2009, 198: 378-386.  (SCI源，计算机学会推荐B类国际期刊）[7]Jie Zhu, Xiaoping Li, Weiming Shen. A divide and conquer based greedy algorithm for 2-machine no-wait job shop problems with makespan minimization. International Journal of Production Research. 2012, 50(10): 2692-2704..（SCI源）[8]Jie Zhu, Bo Gao, Zhihu Wang, Berthold Reinwald, Changjie Guo, Xiaoping Li, Wei Sun. A dynamic resource allocation algorithm for Database-as-a-Service. IEEE International Conference on Web Services. 2011, 564-571. （计算机学会推荐B类国际会议， 录用率仅11%） [9]Jie Zhu, Xiaoping Li. An effective evolutionary algorithm for pre-emptive resource-constrained project scheduling problems. 2010 IEEE International Conference on Systems, Man, and Cybernetics. 1973-1978. (国际高级会议，EI 检索 20110413608507)[10]Jie Zhu, Xiaoping Li, Yi Zhang, Qian Wang. Meta-Heuristic for No-Wait Job Shops with Makespan Minimization. The 12th International Conference on Computer Supported Cooperative Work in Design. 2008; 874-879. (EI 检索 20083711535721)[11]Jie Zhu, Xiaoping Li, Weiming Shen. Effective Genetic Algorithm for Resource- constrained Project Scheduling with Limited Preemptions. International Journal of Machine Learning and Cybernetics. 2011; 2(2): 55-65. (EI检索，Springer新国际期刊)[12]Jie Zhu, Xiaoping Li. An efficient metaheuristic for the blocking job shop problem with makespan minimization. International Conference on Machine Learning and Cybernetics 2011; 1352-1357.3. 主持科研项目[11]国家自然科学青年基金：云计算环境下的多租户共享与动态资源调度理论与方法(Grant No. 71401079), Project Leader, under research.[12]盐城大数据研究院科研项目（横向）：数据中心运营管理与维护系统的建设与产业化, Project Leader, under research.[13]南京邮电大学引进人才项目：云计算环境下多粒度资源共享的资源调度算法研究 (Grant No. NY214016), Project Leader, under research.4. 专利申请[14]朱洁, 朱立华, 沙超. 一种多模块应用弹性配置方法。(国内专利申请号 201410410226.9）[15]朱洁, 秦晋, 张毅, 张楚雄. 实现虚拟机迁移的方法和装置. (PCT 申请号: PCT/CN2012/083057; 国内专利申请号：201280001470.9) .[16]朱洁, 张楚雄, 张毅. 一种应用升级方法、装置. (PCT 申请号PCT/CN2013/081410; 国内专利申请号201380001370.0) [17]朱洁, 张毅, 秦晋. A method for scaling out cloud applications. PCT application No. PCT/CN2014/076057; Domestic Application No. 201480000879.8) Proposed in Huawei.[18]Yi Zhang, Chuxiong Zhang, Jie Zhu. A method of deploying and application on a cloud platform. (PCT application No. PCT/CN2013/083226；Domestic Application No. 201210583901.9) Proposed in Huawei.[19]Yi Zhang, Chuxiong Zhang, Jie Zhu. A method for achieving cloud resources. (PCT application No. PCT/CN2012/087312; Domestic Application No. 201280002031.X) Proposed in Huawei.[20]Yi Zhang, Chuxiong Zhang, Jie Zhu. A method for allocating resources. (PCT application No. PCT/CN2012/078953; Domestic Application No. 201280001190.8) Proposed in Huawei.
</body></doc>