<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<doc><id>80</id><url>http://yjs.njupt.edu.cn/epstar/web/outer/dsfc_ny_.jsp?dsgh=20140089</url><title>余瀚</title><datetime>2018-09-12</datetime><body>
									学生可以获得基金支持完成学业.中国国家自然科学基金青年项目（11501302），2016~2018，基于早至波的非线性反演与成像研究，主持.中国国家自然科学基金面上项目（61571238），2016~2019，基于贝叶斯和有限集统计的多源多尺度异构统计信息融合，参与.南京邮电大学科研启动基金，2015-2017，主持.发表文章1.Han Yu, Dongliang Zhang, and Yunsong Huang. Application of Early Arrival Waveform Inversion with Pseudo-Deconvolution Misfit Function by Source Convolution. Inverse Problems in Science and Engineering, doi: 10.1080/17415977.2016.1138945, 2017. (SCI, IF:0.91) 2.Han Yu, Yunsong Huang, Bowen Guo. Near-surface fault detection by migrating back-scattered surface waves with and without velocity profiles. Journal of Applied Geophysics, doi: 10.1016/j.jappgeo.2016.04.013, vol. 130, pp. 81-90, 2016. (SCI, IF:1.35) 3.Han Yu, and Craig C. Douglas. An Analysis of Infiltration with Moisture Content Distribution in a Two Dimensional Discretized Water Content Domain. Hydrological Processes, doi: 10.1002/hyp.10248, 29(6), pp. 1225-1237, 2015. (SCI, IF: 2.76)  4.Han Yu, and Yunsong Huang. Frequency-Wavenumber Domain Phase Inversion along Reflection Wavepaths. Journal of Applied Geophysics, doi: 10.1016/j.jappgeo.2014.09.012, vol. 111, pp. 14-20, 2014. (SCI, IF:1.35)  5.Han Yu, Dongliang Zhang, and Xin Wang. Application of Weighted Early-arrival Waveform Inversion to Shallow Land Data. Journal of Applied Geophysics, doi: 10.1016/j.jappgeo.2014.01.003, vol. 102, pp. 68-76, 2014. (SCI, IF:1.35)  6.Han Yu, Bowen Guo, and Gerard T. Schuster. Background Velocity Inversion by Phase along Reflection Wave Paths. SEG Technical Program Expanded Abstracts 2014: pp. 3232-3236, doi: 10.1190/segam2014-0011.1. The 84th SEG annual meeting in Denver 2014.  7.Han Yu, Bowen Guo, Sherif Hanafy, Fan-Chi Lin, and Gerard T. Schuster. Direct Detection of Near-surface Faults by Migration of Back-scattered Surface Waves. SEG Technical Program Expanded Abstracts 2014: pp. 2135-2139, doi: 10.1190/segam2014-0737.1. The 84th SEG annual meeting in Denver 2014.  8.Han Yu, and Sherif Hanafy. An Application of Multiscale Early Arrival Waveform Inversion to Shallow Seismic Data. Near Surface Geophysics, doi: 10.3997/1873-0604.2014002, vol. 12(4), pp. 549-557, 2014. (SCI, IF:1.23) </body></doc>